Building websites involves a lot of tedious work.
搭建一个网站往往涉及许多冗长乏味的工作
Even with the simple website that we have been building so
即使是我们目前为止搭建的 这个非常简单的网站
far, you realized that you had to do a lot of work manually.
我们也已经对其做了大量的工作
For example, we had to go and fetch Bootstrap and all the files related
以使用 Bootstrap 为例 我们就需要去到它的网站
to Bootstrap by going to the website and then downloading all the stuff from there.
下载所有的相关文件并把它们放在合适的位置
Then we had to go and fetch and
除了 Bootstrap 以外 在搭建网站时
many other assets that we require for building of our website.
我们往往还需要很多其它的东西
Now, if we need to repetitively do these things,
如果我们需要重复做这些无趣的工作
it becomes extremely cumbersome after a period of time.
你可以想象这将非常枯燥难耐
This is where if we have automation tools that can help us to
所以拥有一个能自动化这些工作的工具
quickly accomplish these tasks with a few commands it would be really beneficial.
就变得很重要了
The note came onto the scene, bringing together the JavaScript run time.
这时 Node 就出现了 它能很好地搭建 JavaScript 运行环境
The web developers suddenly realized that they could easily use the JavaScript
而 web 开发者们有天突然惊觉 他们完全可以用他们已有的 JavaScript 技巧
skills that they already possess to write a whole bunch of tools that help to
来写一整套用来自动化他们 平时反复在做的任务
automate a lot of the tasks that they do day in and day out.
的工具
This is spawned a rich set of tools that have
这之后发展出了一套很丰富的
become widely adopted by the web development community.
被 web 开发社区所广泛接受的工具
Now we are going to review a few of these wonderful tools.
接下来我们将会学习其中一些非常棒的工具
To help us to manage our own web development.
来帮助我们管理我们自己的 web 开发
As I mentioned, there are a lot of tools for doing the development.
正如我已提过的 好用的工具有非常多
We can do review a few of them that will prove very essential
我们将会在这个专项课程中的一些课程中
as you go through the remaining courses of this specialization.
学习其中一些已被证明为十分必要的工具
We will learn these tools just in time and then start immediately applying them
我们会在恰当的时间学习它们 并在学习之后马上应用它们
for helping us to progress in the courses.
它们将会是我们课程进度的助推器
First we will learn about Bower, which is a package manager for the Web.
首先我们将学习 Bower 这个管理包的工具
Then, in the next course, we will learn about Grunt and
然后在下节课里 我们将会学习 Grunt 和 Gulp
Gulp, which are what we call task automation tools.
它们能自动化一些任务工作
Then we'll look at Yo, which is a web app scaffolding tool.
然后我们会看一下 Yo 这个 web 框架搭建器
Now, all these tools have been brought together under this umbrella called
现在 所有我刚刚提到的工具都被囊括进了
Yeoman, which is a workflow that is designed around and using these tools.
一个叫 Yoeman 的东西 事实上 它本身就是被设计成一个使用这些工具的工作流
We are going to learn more about Yeoman in the next course,
我们将会在下一节课中 学习到 Yoeman 的更多知识
but at this moment we are just going to learn specifically about power
不过现在我们将专注于 Bower 这个
which is one of the components in this tool set.
在 Yoeman 工具集中的其中一个工具
Now if you have been doing programming using one of the integrated
如果你有在集成开发环境中编程的经验
development like Visual Studio, Reclipse, and so on you see that there is a lot of
你应该已经发现这些环境整合了许多
integration of tools that help you to get your web accomplished.
帮助我们编程的工具
In the web world, we don't have a single integrated development environment.
在 web 开发中 我们没有这样的集成开发环境
The web developers generally prefer to use a lot of command line tools.
web 开发者们一般偏好于用一系列命令行工具
So the tools that you're going to encounter Power, Grunt, Gulp, and Yo,
这其中我们要接触到的就是 Bower, Grunt, Gulp, Yo 和 Yoeman
and Yeoman, are all command line tools that we gonna execute using a terminal.
这些工具都是在终端里运行的
And all these are built in JavaScript, and they are run using note.
同时 这些工具都是用 JavaScript 写的 并通过 Node 来运行
Right now, we are going to explore Bower in more detail.
接下来我们将学习 Bower 的细节
Bower, as I mentioned, is a package manager for the web.
正如我所提及, Bower 是管理包的工具
Now what does this mean?
这是什么意思呢
When you build a website, we realize that we need to fetch a lot of
当我们搭建一个网站时
packages that we need in building our tool.
我们通常需要许多包
As an example, when we were building our website through the exercises.
比如说我们现在搭建的这个网站
We saw that we went to the Bootstrap website and
就用到了 Bootstrap
fetched the Bootstrap files.
而 Bootstrap 需要去到它的网站来下载
Then we ventured to Font Awesome website and
我们同样去了 Font Awesome 的网站
fetched all the Font Awesome files and so on.
并下载了我们需要的 Font Awesome 文件
So, we had to manually do all these things.
我们之前是人为地完成这些任务的
Now, Bower automates the search for all these web packages,
现在有了 Bower 之后 我们就能自动化这些工作了
as you will see when we go through the exercise next.
我们将会在下一个练习中 学习其具体使用方法
Bower helps us to automatically fetch all these components.
Bower 能自动获取所有这些组件
Not only that, we will notice that if we need to reinstall the components,
而且更厉害的是 当我们需要重装或者更新这些组件时
or update this components, Bower comes to our rescue, okay?
Bower 也能帮我们自动地完成
Now, Bower is one of the tools in the whole tool set
Bower 是我们整个工作流中工具集的
which forms part of our workflow.
其中一个工具
So as we go through, we will learn the remaining tools and
然后再接着 我们将会学习这个工具集中
then imply them to get our work done.
剩下的工具
The best way to learn more about Bower is actually to use it.
学习 Bower 最好的方法就是实际地使用它
In the process we will learn all the commands that we need to understand
在使用它的过程中 我们将会看到我们需要用到的
to employ Bower to get our work done.
所有相关的 Bootstrap 命令
So in the next exercise we're gonna make use of Bower to automatically go and
那么在接下来这个练习里 我们将学习如何使用 Bower 来自动地
fetch for us Bootstrap, Font Awesome from
获取 Bootstrap, Font Awesome 相关的文件
the available packages, web packages.
然后我们将学习如何将 Bower 获取的这些包
And then we'll make use of them in building our website.
应用到我们的网站中 【翻译 - Carefree0910】